[Charli xcx] ♪ 3-6-5,
party girl, bumpin' that ♪
♪ 3-6-5, party
girl, bumpin' that ♪
girl, party girl ♪
♪ 3-6-5, party
girl, bumpin' that ♪
♪ 3-6-5, party girl, party girl
Party girl, party girl ♪
[electronic
dance-pop music playing]
♪ 3-6-5, party
girl, bumpin' that ♪
girl, party girl ♪
♪ 3-6-5, party
girl, bumpin' that ♪
♪ 3-6-5, party girl,
party girl Party girl,
party girl, party girl ♪
♪ Party girl, party girl
Party girl, party girl ♪
♪ When I'm in the club
Yeah, I'm bumpin' that ♪
♪ When I'm at the house
♪ 3-6-5, party
girl, bumpin' that ♪
♪ Shall we do a little key?
Shall we have a little line? ♪
♪ Wanna go real wild
When I'm bumpin' that ♪
♪ Meet me in the bathroom
If you're bumpin' that ♪
♪ 3-6-5, party girl,
bumpin' that 3-6-5, party girl,
bumpin' that ♪
Charli xcx's hit album, Brat,
has not only reached UK number
one, it's just been named word
of the year.
This record proves that Charli
truly is a generational
pop artist.
Everybody is
talking about Brat Summer.
[show host] People are obsessed
over the way that you presented
this music.
-The dance... You have
the apple.
-They say you claimed a color.
[news host]  A slime
green cultural phenomenon.
[Charli] This is the total
opposite of an overnight
success story.
Brat has opened Charli's doors
to more mainstream possibility.
[news host] Now it's been given
a new dictionary definition.
Do you really want brats
to run this country?
They already do enough damage.
Charli! Oh, my God.
Thank goodness you're here.
♪ 3-6-5, 3-6-5 ♪
♪ 3-6-5, 3-6-5, party girl ♪
[gasping, panting]
-[director] Cut!
-[rustling]
[director] Okay,
you wanna go again?
[rustling]
[Charli] Um,
okay. Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
[clattering]
[Charli] Okay.
Hi, it's Charli xcx. You're
listening to [bleep] Breakfast .
Keep having... [sighs]
Are you having a Brat Summer?
I'm sorry, what is it again?
Is it, "I'm Charli xcx,"
or "It's Charli xcx"?
-Once again, we agreed to...
-Lloyd, I just--
"Hi, this is Charli xcx.
You're listening to
[bleep] Breakfast.
Brat Summer forever."
Wait a sec? "It is Charli xcx."
-No. "This is Charli xcx."
-Oh, my God.
Okay. Lloyd, don't
you just think the whole, like,
"Keep having a Brat Summer"
thing is a bit cringe?
I mean, it's...
I mean, it's all cringe.
"Make sure to download
the [bleep] Breakfast app
-to hear my Brat Essentials
playlist."
-You're not listening to me.
And we have to hit the
five-second mark really clean,
so you have to
say it kind of fast.
I'm not gonna do it in
five seconds. It's impossible.
-You're gonna have to do it.
-Well, I'm not gonna.
"And follow @ [bleep] Breakfast
for your chance to win tickets
to my upcoming Brat tour."
-[Lloyd] Good to go again?
-[sighs]
Great. That is great.
Um, [bleep] are gonna be
super happy with that, guys.
-Can we get talking
about schedules? -What? No, Tim.
We haven't gotten
a usable take yet, so...
How many did they want?
-Just--
-I thought it was incredible.
We have three TikToks to make
today. We have to get this in by
end of day.
-I'm not doing it.
-Please.
Get your phone out my face.
Also, we need to schedule a call
about this concert film with
the label.
Did we already agree to that?
I think I should just say,
"Hey, I'm Charli xcx."
You know what?
Fine. You are Charli xcx.
-I am, and you love
that about me. -[laughing]
-Love it.
-[Ana] All right, let's board.
Can you guys
finish that on the flight?
But also, make sure you sleep,
Charli. It's important.
Are you sleeping generally?
-I'm not doing
it on the flight... -Okay.
...by the way. Not even sorry.
Yeah, noted. Okay.
[Tim] No. Don't look at
the camera? Oh, no. I won't.
Oh, did I?
Do you have your passport?
[Lloyd] Ana, if you ask me about
my passport one more time...
You guys have sorted all
that Brat concert film
stuff, right?
Yeah.
Because we've got
the Americans coming in.
Right. Yeah, 100%. All right...
-Alex? Good?
-Yeah.
-Dressed like me today.
-We good?
-Gonna have a fake tan next?
-Yes, Lee.
-Maybe take the jacket off. -You
think the jacket's too much?
I don't want them to think
we're, like,
doing a whole mini-me...
Yeah, sure.
Mic test, mic test, mic test.
-[Jamie] The Americans are
coming. -[Josh] There's fucking
millions of them.
[Jamie] Tammy, welcome.
Yeah. So, again, thank
you guys so much for coming over
for this.
Should we do a quick round
of introductions?
-I'm Jamie.
-[Tammy] No.
Let's just get
right into it. Charli xcx.
Been a great summer, huh?
How do we keep
this Brat thing going?
Yeah, Josh, do you wanna...
Absolutely.
Um, so... [clears throat] ...
you know, we've-- we've
obviously been blown away
by how massive all of the
Brat Summer stuff has gotten.
How do we go from this big
fucking moment and keep
it exciting?
You know, keep it alive?
Because obviously,
we've always known
that Charli is just, like,
a really innovative artist,
you know?
I mean, she is super creative.
But, I mean,
this level of success.
I don't know if any of us
could've predicted...
Yeah. She's always had
her niche little thing going on.
But now, it's fucking mental.
Yeah, so, rather than rushing
to the next thing,
stick to what's working, right?
So, Charli xcx concert film?
Yes. We've got Amazon financing,
so that's fantastic.
I mean, this could be our way
of keeping Brat fresh till...
well, like,
next summer. [chuckles]
Um, we've actually managed
to get the fucking guy.
-We got Johannes Godwin.
-Yeah.
He's, like, the director.
Does all of the big shows.
-Katy, Justin...
-I think Johannes is great for
this, I do.
It's assuming that Charli and
her team are aligned with
everything, right?
Yeah. I mean,
she's just buzzing for it.
Um, she's just, like, over
the moon with the whole plan
as far as we're aware, um...
So, we just really want to get
this thing going, like,
yesterday.
Yesterday? Well,
that's impossible.
Yeah. No, of course. [chuckles]
Um, we just... we're feeling
really, really good about it.
[Tammy] Okay, good.
So, the, uh, Howard Stirling
activation is this week.
You know,
the banking thing? Brat coin?
-Something like that. -It's
a card. It's a... a Brat card.
[Tammy] Whatever. Bye. Bye.
-[Jamie] Thank you so much. Yes.
-[Josh] Thank you, Tammy!
[Josh] I absolutely
fucking killed that.
-Like flipped it.
-Oh, my God.
-When you offhanded to
me, I was like... -Fucking hell.
I know, I know. It was, like,
um, those guys in, uh,
basketball.
-Jordan and that. Crazy.
-Yeah. Fucking sick.
[host 1]  Well,
there you have it. Charli xcx.
What an incredible
run she's had.
Virtually unknown last year and
now she's hit the mainstream.
[host 2]  Bet she's
feeling chuffed with herself.
[host 1] Do you think Charli's
thinking about what's next?
[host 2] We definitely are.
Now that Brat Summer's coming
to an end,
we're playing the artists
we think will soundtrack
your next few months.
Stick around to
hear who's next up.
Um, okay, so, we've got a call
booked for 9:00 a.m. tomorrow.
We are gonna have to do the Zoom
call for the concert film
on the way to the Vogue shoot.
Tim said there'd be
no other time to do it.
Okay, fine.
Okay. And then, I was looking
into, like, a couple days for
you to take a vacation.
We do still have that offer for
Ibiza. It's real easy, like,
literally one post.
Yeah, but, Ana, why would I be
taking a vacation right now?
I mean...
[Ana] Okay.
I'm about to start rehearsals
for tour. Like, it would be
crazy for me to go away.
-Yeah.
-Come on.
[Charli sighs]
-There's just so much happening,
you know? -[Ana] Okay.
[Charli] Sorry.
-[Ana] Good night.
-[card reader beeps]
[Colbert] That was a look at
her festival shows from earlier
this summer.
Soon, she'll begin her first
ever arena headlining tour.
Here to tell us all about it,
please welcome Charli xcx!
[studio audience cheering]
So nice to have you on. I've
been looking forward to this.
How does it feel to have claimed
a whole summer?
[Charli laughs]
Not many people can say
that they've done that.
I think basically,
at this point,
it's you and the Son of Sam.
Wow. Great
company to be in, um--
Yeah, I mean, it just
kind of happened, Stephen.
And you've just announced--
I wanna get this right--
you're headlining
a tour that's apparently
"going to be bigger and better
than anything we've seen from
you before."
Are you partying
straight into Brat autumn?
[Charli chuckles]
[Colbert]  Is it gonna
be the apple cider dance?
Have you ever snorted
a rail of pumpkin spice?
[studio audience
laughing, applauding]
You know what,
as of yet, I have not.
But... I love to party.
- It's a full-time job,
babe. You know?  - Oh, my God.
So, is this
the big Brat send-off?
Is it the end of an era?
Um... [chuckles]
Um, great question. Uh...
I don't-- I don't
know. I mean, uh...  [chuckles]
I guess we'll just have
to wait and see, I suppose.
And, uh... I mean, you'll be
there. I hear you love a party.
- Oh, it's a full-time job,
baby.  -[studio audience
laughing, cheering]
- Thanks so much for being here.
- Thank you.
Tickets to her Brat tour are on
sale now. Charli xcx, everybody.
[cheering continues, fades]
[alarm ringing]
[Tim] Um, okay.
Morning, morning, morning.
[Ana] Did you get that email?
Oh, yes. Shit.
We've got a call now on Zoom
about the concert film.
It's with the label and
the director to make sure you're
happy with him.
That's not reaching. What's--
What's the director's name?
Johannes?
[Tim] Jannis.
Oh, my God. Right,
it's not gonna reach. Sorry.
We're gonna have to swap sides.
Let's swap sides.
I'm sorry. I know you don't
like going backwards.
-It's fine. Let's just do it.
-Okay.
[Tim coughs,
clears throat] Okay.
Um... [clears throat]
-All right, I'm... I think I'm
on. -[Tim] You're on? I'm on.
We're on.
-Hello.
-Hi.
- Hi. I'm here with Tammy.
-[Tammy] Charli.
Charli, we're connecting you
with the amazing Johannes,
your director
for the concert film.
- Hey, Charli!
-Hi.
- Huge fan. Very, very nice to
meet you.  -Thanks. Thank you.
Uh, Tammy, thank you, thank you,
thank you for setting this up.
And, Charli, I just want to say
that I love the new album,
and I can't wait to
jump into the trenches with you.
I have a couple of,
um, pretty wild ideas
that I'm excited to share
with you when we meet in person.
[Charli] Cool.
Is Celeste gonna join this call?
-Celeste?
-Yeah. It's fine.
-Just tell me after.
-Sorry, sorry.
Sorry, just to be clear,
I already have my tour
creative sorted,
so we're just looking for
someone to come and capture it.
Um, is that something
that you do then, or...
Uh, I'm sure once we meet in
person, we'll figure out...
We'll make sure...
[Tammy] Tim. I think there
has been a misunderstanding.
[Tim] Yeah. All good.
[Tim mutters] No?
[Tammy] Can we sidebar
about this ASAP, please?
Sorry, um, this sort of
thing cracks up. I-I-I'm--
Sorry, me and Charli just need
to connect heads on
that a little bit.
Everything's moving so fast at
the moment as you can imagine,
but we are very, very excited.
[chuckles]
[Johannes] So, awesome.
Thank you, uh, everyone.
Have a great day.
See you soon.
All right. Thank you.
-Bye-bye.
-[Charli] Thanks. Yeah.
Why wasn't Celeste on that call?
-He's got ideas. Like... -Well,
she can be. We can loop her in.
Well, yeah, I mean,
she's supposed to be my creative
director.
She's the one who's supposed to
be dealing with all of
this stuff.
I mean, she's the only one
who fucking gets it, Tim.
-I need her on these things.
-If that's what you prefer.
Yes, I would.
I would prefer that.
Okay. Then we'll... Yeah.
Have you gotten a chance to read
that book I got you
about the psychic
horse who cures cancer?
-No, I haven't. Not yet.
-Oh, my God.
You have to get to it.
It's just been so busy
and hectic, you know, Molly.
Of course. Of course, no.
I was up all night listening
to the audiobook again.
I could not sleep a wink.
That stomach thing.
Do you remember that?
It's coming back as it always
does, and I don't know why
this time.
It's not even something
that I ate.
I've only been eating pears.
I mean, Molly, I just--
I can't get sick, you know?
The pain is unbearable. Hmm? Oh,
no. You're not gonna get sick.
The only person that could get
you sick is me,
and I'm not sick.
-Are you-- You're sure?
Definitely? -No,
never been sick.
Mm-hmm.
Tell me that you're not
drinking water again.
Two cups a day,
maximum. I'm not kidding.
-Hey, Charli, um...
-Hey.
Just want to touch base on what
Mel and the Vogue team have put
together
-for your look today.
-[Charli] Uh-huh.
We're feeling so excited.
Yeah, so, I don't know
if you've seen the set,
but it's not what I thought
it was gonna be,
but I have an idea.
Like, I wanna put you in
something more glamorous,
more you,
-like, so, it's like,
a juxtaposition. -[Charli] Yeah.
You know what I mean?
[Mel] It's gonna be tiny,
so I need to stitch you into
it standing up, like,
Marilyn style.
Susie will stitch you into it.
I need to let the crew know ASAP
if she's gonna be standing.
-Is she gonna be stand-- Okay.
Okay. -She's standing. Yeah.
She's gonna be
standing, apparently.
Can we figure
out how to do that?
Um, yeah, just
get everything up.
Um, maybe put
it on a tall table.
Sorry, can I just ask, um...
Is it gonna look
weird if I'm standing?
Like, has anyone ever done
a "what's in my bag" standing
up before?
Um, well, if it's important
to Mel, we can make it happen.
And it sounds like
it is important to Mel.
Um, but no, no.
We've never done it standing.
Maybe, if you're feeling good
in the center region,
we can try it crouching
and stitch it like that.
-Do you know-- -I don't
know if that's better, babe.
[crew chattering]
Babe, they keep asking what's in
your bag.
Do you know what's in your bag?
Um, no. Just figure it out.
-I'm sorry. I don't have a clue.
-[scoffs]
Okay, Tim, um, we really need to
talk about this whole concert
film situation.
[Tim] Yes, yes, yes.
I just feel like the director
was really weird, you know?
[Tim] Johannes, yeah.
Yeah, whatever his name is.
Have you seen
the films that he makes?
I mean, he basically
makes adverts for women.
Uh, adverts for women? Sorry?
No, I mean, an advert of
a woman. Like,
the woman is the advert.
Isn't that the same thing?
Like, he's done loads of stuff.
Like, Alex actually told me
he invented The Ma--
You're not gonna care, but
he invented The Masked Singer .
[Molly gasps]
-Are you serious?
-[Charli] You're right. I don't.
When do we need
to decide this by?
'Cause I think Celeste should
just send through some other
options.
Um, it is worth you knowing
that everyone is really excited
about Johannes.
Everyone? What do you mean,
everyone? The label? Jamie?
I don't give a fuck
what they think, you know?
It's most important that
I think this guy is cool.
That should obviously be the
priority in this situation, Tim.
-That's what I've been saying
for years. -Thanks, Molly.
Thank you, Molly. Um...
Uh... Okay. Let's all have
a conversation now.
Get it out of the way.
Let's talk to
Ana, who's on the phone.
Where's Lloyd?
I don't know. I think he's gone
to find out what's in my bag.
[sniffs]
It's tight.
I just think if
it's, like, one inch,
or, like, meters,
or whatever you guys call it.
Like, that is... it's gonna go.
Hi, British Vogue. I'm Charli
xcx, and this is what's
in my bag.
Never...
Cards...
...a great scent.
I wish I had a brand
deal with them. An extra...
Sunglasses.
And that was what was in my bag.
-[Charli] There it is.
-[Celeste] Wow.
[Charli] Oh, amazing.
-They're saying I've got scurvy.
-It's great.
-That's good. You look--
-Is it? Is that good?
It means you look...
-What does that mean, I look
like-- Okay. -...thin. [laughs]
I actually don't know
what scurvy makes you look like.
-Me neither.
-Does it make you green?
[Charli] Oh, God. Well, that
would be on-brand, wouldn't it?
-Okay, Celeste. I'm distracting
us. -[Celeste] You ready?
Do whatever this is.
-The tour, take me through the
show... -[Celeste] Do, do, do.
...take me through the show.
So, we have good news today,
which is that we are going to
do full rain on B stage for
track 10.
-[Charli] Wow. Amazing.
-Very exciting.
[Celeste] And then I sent
the list of our directors
that we went over,
and I have four
Steadicam guys down...
Okay, babe,
they already hired that guy.
[Celeste] What guy?
The fucking...
-[Celeste] No.
-The guy. They hired-- Yeah.
-Everybody was, like,
giving a lot of... -Charli.
[Charli] ...like,
input and getting involved.
Then there was also
that fucking Zoom call.
[Celeste] I cannot believe
that I wasn't on this call.
Yeah. And they all seem to
kind of feel like
-they know what is best
for me, and-- -Which is what?
Well, what do you think? It's
like, Brat, Brat, Brat, Brat .
More Brat . Brat forever.
And you know what?
Maybe they're right.
Yeah, but, Charli, if you don't
wanna make a tour film,
-and you don't like this
director... -[Charli sighs]
...you just say no.
-That's how this goes.
-Yeah. I just...
I feel like it's kind of
a big deal, though, you know?
Like, I've never been
in this position before.
No one's ever asked me
to do this kind of thing.
You know?
[Celeste] Yeah, we've just been
waiting for everybody to
catch up.
Yeah, and now they fucking have.
I just feel like if
I don't do the concert film,
then we've just got the tour,
then it's the end.
You're not gonna
die after an album cycle.
-[chuckles] Are you?
-[Charli] I don't know. I might!
-You might? You might?
-[laughing]
[Celeste] You're gonna
let Brat go at some point.
So you can either do it the way
that you wanna do it,
or somebody else
is gonna fuck it up for you.
Okay, well... I mean, obviously
if those are the options,
I'm fucking it up.
[Celeste] Great.
So let's fuck it up.
-Okay, great.
-Great.
-Show me the... what-- I don't
know. -[Celeste laughing]
What were you talking
about? Strobes? I don't know.
[Tim] Ana, have
you noticed the lights?
-[Ana] Yeah.
-[Tim] Sort of karaoke vibes.
[Tim singing] ♪
Back to back to... ♪
Well...
Oh, Charli, actually,
we need to talk about something.
Um, Charli?
Charli?
Hi.
Um, yes, so, this event,
I think sort of everyone's gonna
be there.
The label were very
involved in this one.
It's sort of their baby.
They set the whole thing up.
They're hoping you're gonna post
quite a lot about it.
[Charli] Okay.
What is it, exactly?
Oh, it's a credit card.
Yeah, yeah, but-- but, like,
a new kind of credit card
for, uh...
For, like, different people.
Like, not, like, normal people.
Not normal people?
No, no.
[stammers] Genuinely,
what-- what was it, Ana?
It's a credit card and savings
account aimed at young
queer people.
So, like, your fans.
And when they sign up, they get
a free ticket to your tour.
It's just a way of bringing in
the younger market.
I actually think it's quite
cool. The card's Brat green.
I want to get one myself.
I won't. But I would if I was,
you know...
But I'm an ally, so...
How do you know they're gay?
[stammers] How do I know?
What do you mean?
The people getting the card,
do they have to prove
that they're gay?
I think that feels insane.
I think it's just more of, like,
a demographic thing.
Yeah. And, like, you can
kind of... you can tell. Right?
Do you know what I mean?
No? Not-- No, you don't.
As in, they know. The people who
are gay know that they are gay.
God. Isn't it just
a little bit fucking lame
for me to be the face
of a credit card, you know?
It's not your face that's gonna
be on it. It's just
that the card is green.
[Charli] Fine.
Guess I'm doing it, aren't I?
[Tim] Should we just
go a little bit clearer?
Um...
Go ahead. Go, go, go.
Um, actually, do you know what,
Charli? I think maybe--
Ooh, sorry.
I think maybe hang tight.
You don't wanna be surrounded
by people wearing lanyards.
I'm on your side.
I'm-- Okay. [sighs]
[sighs]
You're looking
very smart today, ma'am.
-Thanks.
-A special event or something?
Oh, just an event. Yeah.
-Singing? Singing?
-Yeah.
What sort of stuff do you sing?
Um, it's, like, dance-pop music.
Oh! You've-- [exhales] You got
me. Hook, line, and sinker.
-I love that stuff.
-Oh, yeah?
Yeah. I love it.
A bit like Leona Lewis?
I love her. I love her.
Drove her a couple of times.
So what was your name again?
What did you say your name
was again?
-Charli xcx.
-[tapping on phone keyboard]
Charli... That top one, is it?
No, that's Charlie Puth.
Yeah. It's the bottom one,
actually,
on that list of Charlies.
Wow. Okay. Oh, yeah!
[exhales]
-Bosh. Look at you there.
-Mmm.
Oh! Look how
different you look there.
Yeah. That's me.
In Amsterdam as well.
Been there a couple of times.
-Oi, oi.
-Oh, yeah. Really?
-Yeah, with the lads and that.
-Yeah.
Yeah. It was for this movie
about kids with cancer.
-[song playing on phone]
-Oh, Christ.
Is that why
you've got the wig on?
-Nope. Not a wig.
-[door opens]
Tim is coming. Thank God. Okay,
and he brought literally
everyone.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
There's loads of lanyard
people. Just--
-Sorry. Sorry, guys.
Just watch-- Yes.
-There's so many people.
No, I-- Yes. I know. It may
seem like that. Sorry. Hi.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
We're just gonna
head straight through...
I think what happened was,
I said, "Don't come with me."
But they just
heard, "Come with me."
Tim, what the fuck is this?
I'm obviously not doing a single
fucking post about this.
[Lloyd] Howard Stirling? Didn't
these guys almost go bankrupt?
[Tammy] Charli xcx!
-Hello. Hello.
-Hi, Tammy.
Hello, Tim.
-Hi! Hi, hi.
-It's so great to see--
You know, my
kids just love Brat.
-Love it. It's so cool.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah. We're really proud.
-Thank you so much.
-You've done so great
for us. Yeah. -Thank you.
-Charli, this is--
-Okay, and this is--
I'm sorry. This is the lawyer
with Howard Stirling.
-Yeah.
-What? Who?
-The bank. Yeah.
-The bank. Yes.
This is the first, first
partnership for Atlantic,
so we're all
really excited about it.
-Wait. Can I jump in... -So
go do your thing. Do your thing.
...for the terms and conditions
of your contract?
Who's this hot little blonde?
Johannes!
-Mmm. [kisses]
-Hey, Tammy.
So good to see you.
Thank you for doing this,
really. It means a lot to us.
It really does.
We can't wait for you to
work your magic with Charli.
I mean, you're so busy.
I'm never too
busy for you. Never.
This is a combination
of what we call warranties and--
We're doing this here. Ana,
we're doing this here,
apparently?
This is part
nine of the agreement.
Neither party may
assign their rights or powers
within the written consent
of the other party.
I heard about
this mess, this case.
See, this is what happens when
you work with another label.
-I mean, it's a total
fucking nightmare. -Yeah.
Do you need any help or support?
I have a great lawyer for you.
Yeah. Artists can
be complicated, right?
That's why we love 'em.
But yeah, no, the whole
situation is kind of sad.
She's clearly fixated on money,
ownership, possessions.
At the end of the day,
they have zero value.
It's what my
father always told me.
He had nothing
when he left Africa.
Mmm. It's amazing what people
think they can get away with.
-You're African?
-Hundred percent.
I'm so sorry, Tammy.
They exploded your luggage.
-Again?
-Yeah.
All social media content
must be pre-approved
with the relevant parties and
aligned with legal prior to
posting.
[emcee] Here we go, everybody.
-Um, yeah. That all sounds
great. -[emcee] Five minutes.
-Charli xcx. Are we ready?
-Right, good.
Well, I just need
your verbal consent.
Um, how do I give you
my verbal consent, sorry?
Well, you just s-- just say.
Oh. Uh, yes.
No?
-Oh. I consent. Great.
-"I consent." That's great.
That's all
I need. Okay. Thank you.
-Ana, can I give
you this, please? -Yeah.
Thank you.
Very quickly, we're just gonna
get you miked very quickly.
Yeah, sure.
Morgh is gonna take care of you,
make sure you have
a fantastic seat,
'cause I want you to see
everything she does,
what she's all about.
-Have we had a sound check yet?
-Nope. I've just got here.
-Okay.
-Okay, nice and quick.
-I can't hear you now I've got
these in. -Okay, that's fine.
Good luck.
-[audience cheering]
-What?
[electronic
dance-pop music playing]
♪ I went my own way and I made
it I'm your favorite
reference, baby ♪
[song continues playing]
-Who's next? Who's next?
-Hello. Hi.
-Hey.
-It's nice to meet you. Hi.
-Charli?
-Hi. Hello.
I love you so much. I mean,
you saved my life, literally.
Just hold up the card nicely.
Okay, big smiles, everyone.
Thank you. And I-I
drew this picture of you.
I tried to kill myself,
but your music saved me.
-I listen to track ten
every day-- -This is so good!
-We need to wrap it up.
-Okay, wait, wait, wait...
Great, great.
-Thank you!
-Love you so much.
Thank you. I'm so
excited about the Brat card.
[publicist]
Who's next? Who's next?
-Hello. Hi.
-Hello.
Big smiles, big smiles.
[chattering]
-Hi, thank you for having us.
-Hi. No problem.
-Hi, love.
-Hey.
I'm gonna head to the bar.
[electronic
dance-pop music playing]
-[Celeste] What does it taste
like? -[Lloyd] Um,
lighter fluid.
But then, how do you swallow it?
You just shoot it. You just
throw it back. Mentally,
there's zero comedown.
-Oh, my God! Charli!
-Oh, my God. Hi.
-Hi. Hi.
-Hi.
-Hi! You were on the shoot. Yes.
-Hi. Yes, the video.
-I had no idea you were in town.
-Yeah, I'm here.
-I'm, like, in and out...
-Yeah.
I've been, like, traveling so
much and, like,
working all the time.
-Yeah. -I haven't seen
you since the "360" video.
I know. That was so much fun.
It was, like, the best day ever.
Yeah, it was really good.
Um...
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry if my,
like, agent overstepped with
that, by the way.
I have, like, zero
control over him. He's crazy.
But then I heard, like,
it got kind of complicated
signing my release.
-Yeah, it did.
I mean, the video... -Really?
...basically
nearly didn't come out.
They put in all these, like,
crazy VFX requests.
Like, we barely
had the budget for it.
It's, like, loads and loads
of retouching from your team.
-I mean, it was a lot
of retouching. -Really?
I was on Accutane at the time.
-Oh. Got it. Got it.
-Yeah.
-Put it on that.
-Yes, thank you.
[Charli] Oh... Oh, my God. Okay.
-Um, Charli, there's...
-Wait. No, no, no. It's fine.
-They're with me,
so just don't worry. -Oh, okay.
-We're deleting this? [chuckles]
-Yes.
Delete this. [chuckles]
I was, like...
There was a little
creep in the bathroom.
Are you doing, like,
a Joaquin Phoenix kinda thing?
Um, yeah. I think so, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Wait, shut the fuck up.
-Wait, shut the fuck up.
-[Lloyd] You like that?
-This is real?
-Yeah.
I thought this was literally
a joke. I need to get one.
[Celeste] You can get one,
right? You're bi or whatever?
[Charli laughs]
Or that was, like, a PR thing?
I've always wondered.
I'm, like, a two
on the Kinsey scale.
-Okay, cool, cool, cool.
-It's enough.
-[Lloyd] Babe, is this big
enough? -[Rachel] Oh, my God.
That's huge.
Maybe just a little-- Maybe
combine them. Yep,
a tiny bit more.
-Yeah.
-[chattering] -[electronic
dance-pop music continues]
Wait, can we take a pic?
Looking hot.
Thank you.
Can you check my
outfit for me? Am I good?
-Is it good? -[Celeste]
I think it goes like that.
It's amazing you call this
an outfit. [laughing] It's
literally just underwear.
[Charli] I kind of love it.
-Oh, my God. There they are!
-We're coming!
-Yeah.
-[music continues playing]
Let's get another drink.
Okay, you... You lead me.
I can't see a fucking thing.
Whoo!
[phone alarm ringing]
[Charli] I didn't realize
this was gonna be so early.
You slept, right?
[Lloyd] What the fuck is
a Piri Piri Hut? Where are we?
[Tim] Dagenham... We literally
spoke about-- Never mind.
-How long are we here?
-[Ana] Two weeks.
Jesus.
You said that you wanted to be
here for the duration of
rehearsals.
I did. I thought
we were gonna be in London.
Oh, the-- the label has checked
to see how you're feeling about
the Johannes plan.
I don't even know what plans
you're talking about.
You haven't sent me any plans.
[Tim] The plan
for the concert film,
because everyone's gonna
be there today, and I didn't...
Is Johannes gonna be there?
He's just shooting the show,
so I'm not sure why he'd be at
rehearsal.
Okay, all right. Okay,
we'll just-- we can iron it out
when we get there.
It's fine.
Look. The Cobrasnake photos
from last night. These are good.
-Oh, yeah. Oh, my God!
-[gasps, chuckles]
Okay. Sorry to break up
the first time you've ever been
on your phones,
but we've arrived at rehearsals.
[Lloyd] Wow.
Wait, you've got two packs.
Why do you have two packs?
These guys, they're filming.
They're, like, filming something
about Charli.
-Hi, hi, hi, hi.
-Hi, babe. Hi.
How are you?
Sorry, I can't move.
[Celeste] The good news is,
like, we're kind of on schedule,
-so I'm feeling good.
-That's good.
-[Charli] Great! That's great!
-But I just, you know.
-The curtains needs to be-- Oh,
yeah. -Hi.
Sorry to interrupt you guys.
-Hi, I'm Charli. Hey.
-You know Brian and Ricky.
They worked on Sweat and Crash.
-Oh. Well, we'll do it again.
-[Celeste] Yeah.
-Hi. Hi, you guys.
-Hi. Hello. Hi.
Killing it obviously.
Good to see you.
-I'll go and do the fitting,
yeah. Okay. -Great, great.
-All right. See you in a bit.
-Yeah.
[Charli] It's
fucking freezing in here.
[Ana] We managed to clear your
schedule for the next few weeks
so you can just
focus on the show.
And there's bird shit on there.
How did a bird get in here?
[Charli] What about... When I
kind of do, you know, all my...
-Is it weird when I do that?
-No, I like it.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
Like this.
Yeah, it looks good.
-It doesn't look weird?
-No.
Okay.
I like it.
I'm getting this
bald spot right here.
-What?
-Yeah.
-My hair, just there.
-Ew.
It's so bad.
It's from these two little
pieces where you kind of pull
them up like that
so that my face gets, like,
super snatched, you know?
Doesn't that hurt?
Well, yeah, but, I mean,
it's a facelift, so...
You should really
give it a rest, you know?
Just, like, before
this shit gets out of hand.
Yeah.
If you keep fucking with it like
that, it's just gonna get worse.
Well, obviously. That's what I'm
saying. I'm going bald, so...
I'm sorry.
[Charli sighs] It's fine.
Um, I'm really sorry
that you had to cancel your
honeymoon, by the way, again.
Don't worry about
it. It's totally fine.
Tyler hates me right now,
but it's gonna be fin--
It's the tour. It's the tour,
babe. I'm not missing the tour
for anything.
And besides, we're just
postponing it a few weeks.
A few weeks?
Yeah. I mean,
you'll be done by then.
The tour will be over, and,
like, this will be finished,
you know?
Done? [scoffs]
It's not gonna be done, is it?
I mean, I'm not gonna be
finished.
It's not gonna be finished.
I don't really know what
you mean by that.
There's so much other stuff.
We've got loads of other things
that I'm doing, actually,
like, loads.
Just get that... Sorry. Just...
Um...
I just wouldn't want you to
have to postpone it again.
That's all.
That's why I'm bringing it up.
Um... I have this
other skirt thingy.
It's sluttier, which I think
is better. I think it's cool.
-Thank you.
-Of course.
[Charli] Looks really good.
♪ I'm everywhere... ♪
Okay...
[crew member]
Here we go. Three, two, one...
-[Charli] Uh-uh.
-[crew member] Drop!
[Celeste] Oh, for fuck's sake.
[Celeste] I'm so sorry.
That will never happen again.
[Charli, Celeste chuckling]
-It's fine.
-Or it might happen twice more.
[electronic
dance-pop music playing]
[Charli on playback] ♪ I
don't wanna share the space ♪
♪ I don't wanna force a smile ♪
♪ This one girl
taps my insecurities ♪
♪ I'm embarrassed to have it
But need the sympathy ♪
♪ 'Cause I couldn't even be her
If I tried ♪
♪ I'm opposite,
I'm on the other side ♪
♪ I feel all these feelings
I can't control ♪
♪ Oh, no, don't know why ♪
♪ All this
sympathy is just a knife ♪
♪ Why I can't even
grit my teeth and lie ♪
♪ I feel all these feelings
I can't control ♪
♪ All this
sympathy is just a knife ♪
♪ Oh, no, oh, no ♪
Whoo!
[laughs] Yeah! Fucking awesome!
-[Charli] Hi, Jamie. Hi.
-Wow!
Uh, thanks. I'll come down
so we can chat. Yeah.
-[Celeste] Can we get...
Can we get the... -It was
fucking phenomenal, Charli.
-[Jamie] Phenomenal.
-Thank you. Thank you.
Um, I wasn't really performing,
uh, just sort of playing
with some ideas and...
-That was all right. Wow.
-Totally. Totally, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
-But it looks fucking sick.
-Oh. Thank you.
-You know these guys, right?
-Yes, uh...
[Johannes] It's good to be back.
I've been holed up in here
with quite a few artists.
Some pretty fun memories.
Uh...
Abel had an issue
with the sound system last year,
but sounds like
they figured that out.
-Sounds pretty good.
-Lucky for you.
Sounds great to me.
You must be
Johannes. Hi, I'm Charli.
I am indeed.
Pleasure to finally meet you.
Yeah, you too. You too.
Hi.
Uh...
So you guys came all this way
just for this?
-[Johannes] Totally.
-Wow.
Of course. Yeah. We've got to
keep the Brat stuff
going, right?
We're staying the whole time.
[Charli] Yeah. Great. [chuckles]
Uh...
-It's so great
you guys are here... -Yes.
-I just need a few--
-I'm Johannes by the way.
-Hi, I'm Celeste. Yeah.
-Hey.
-You work with Charli? Awesome.
-I work with Charli, yeah.
We just gotta keep
going through this so...
-Yeah, yeah, of course.
-...if you wanna like,
-all just come back or
whatever... -Guys, guys.
We're gonna let you guys do
your thing. We're not even here.
-Thank you. Yeah. Okay, okay.
-We're not even here.
-[Johannes] Phones
off, guys. Phones off. -Yeah.
-[Jamie] Another level.
-[Johannes] This is
a sacred space.
[Charli] Okay, um...
Thanks for all coming, guys.
-[scattered applause] -Oh,
no, don't... don't... It's...
I'll just sing it again, yeah?
[electronic
dance-pop music playing]
-[Celeste] At the top?
-[Charli] Yeah.
-Do you know...
-On the, like... [vocalizing]
Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
-You know what I mean?
Yep. Yeah.
[Charli] Like,
I think we need to maybe just...
[Charli on playback]
♪ When I go to the club ♪
♪ I wanna hear
those club classics ♪
Can I say something?
-[music continues, stops] -Can
we stop? Sorry, can we stop?
Thank you.
Um, I feel like
there's a light missing.
-Like, more at the top?
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just... I don't know, I think
we could add something there.
-Totally. -Feels like
there's a space that...
-Great.
-I...
-Sorry, that... I wanna fill it.
-Maybe... Great. We'll fill it.
And also, like, I really like
what's happening with
the screens.
-The screens? Great. Great.
-Yeah.
Hi. Hey, um...
So...
Sorry, um...
I'm probably being a bit crazy
right now, but you're listening
quite a lot.
I'm sure
that you have to do that
for whatever the thing is
that you're doing,
but I just don't
really know who you are
and it's kinda making me
not able to concentrate.
-So it just feels a bit...
-Sorry, excuse me.
Do not apologize.
-That is totally our bad.
-Yeah.
-Right, right.
-We apologize.
-Not you. It won't happen again.
-It's not--
-It's okay. Don't worry.
I'm just... -Sorry about that.
-I'm probably being a bit
intense myself.
-It won't happen again.
Keep listening
but just less intense.
-Apologies. Apologies for that.
-Just...
Um...
-Charli, can I... go ahead?
-Yes? Yeah? Mm-hmm.
I just wanna show
you the strobing section
that comes right after, so...
-Can we... Great.
-Okay. Show me. Show me.
Go for it.
[electronic
dance-pop music resumes]
[music stops]
-Um...
-Something in that realm?
Um... [stammers]
Is it kind of p... painful?
[Celeste] I like
it. It's kind of, like...
-It's kind of
strong for the top. -Yeah.
Totally. Totally, totally.
[Johannes clears throat]
[Celeste] Sorry?
-[Johannes] Sorry?
-Did you say something?
-Did-- No.
-Yeah.
No, I'm just...
We're here to observe.
You guys have such a beautiful
flow going here. It's inspiring.
Okay. Um...
However, if I could just
interject one little thing...
Yeah?
I think it's just really
important to hear out Charli's
concern here.
Um, 'cause w-we don't wanna
alienate the audience, right?
Yeah, well, I don't... I don't
think it's alienating, but...
No?
Okay, well, first of all, thank
you for sharing your thought.
And I do hear you,
but I still think some of these
elements will probably turn some
people off.
Um, bouncing off of that,
is Amazon might have some things
to flag there, Charli.
Um, obviously, all of
your amazing creative stuff is
the priority.
It's just there might have to be
a few things that we may have to
compromise.
Compromise? Like, this is the
show. You're watching the show.
Totally. I don't think it's
a compromise,
I think it's an opportunity.
-[Celeste] Great. Great.
-Exactly.
It's an opportunity for Charli
to reach out to a whole new
audience,
so that Brat , this amazing
moment, can last much longer.
Maybe even forever.
That's the goal, isn't it?
-I mean, I don't think
that's the goal. -Yeah. No.
We make another record.
Charli, listen, you have this
awesome just "F you" energy and
I love that.
People love that.
It's important for you to be
true to yourself and
who you are.
We also don't wanna offend
or exclude anyone, right?
'Cause a-a family might be
watching this film.
That family will
turn off the television.
We don't want that,
do we? Like... Right?
Sorry, I'm really
confused right now.
She's singing about cocaine.
Like, aren't we all on the same
page? Like,
this is not a PG show.
-Is she...
-Is she what?
...literally singing about
"cocaine" cocaine or
metaphorically?
What's metaphorical cocaine?
[Tim] Sorry to interrupt,
I just wondered if I could
borrow our Charli
-for a second.
-Yes, yes.
-They wanna discuss
a new Magnum flavor. -Great!
-Sorry if I'm interrupting.
-No, you're not.
Um, it's a good time actually
'cause I think you guys should
chat more
-and figure out all
of this stuff. -Yeah.
I love the strobes, um...
But I don't know. You know?
I don't-- I don't actually know.
Okay. Let's do that thing
that you just said we're doing.
Thank you. Sorry.
-[Johannes] Thank you. Thank
you. -Do you have my stuff?
Yes, yeah. Just down here.
It's great.
We're coming up with new things,
we're tweaking little things,
but quite a bit of it was good.
-Yeah. It's good.
-Yeah, yeah.
[Johannes] Let's
see what we can do...
-Tweak--
-Let's go for a playback.
[Jamie] Okay.
And you should be really proud.
-Awesome.
-Thank you. Thank you so much.
[Johannes] Yeah.
That was weird.
Oh, no. What
was... Wh-Who was weird?
I mean... everything.
Like, there were just a million
random people staring at me
and... I don't know.
It was just weird. You know?
And plus Celeste is, like,
arguing with everyone.
-Hmm.
-You listening?
Yeah. Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course, sorry.
Uh, what... Celeste.
What was Celeste upset about?
I don't know. I mean,
it was just, like,
really tense in there.
Why did we have that many people
in rehearsal, you know?
Because they were all just
standing there watching me
while I'm trying to make
a fucking decision.
Right. Yeah, no. That...
Okay, that's not good and I will
definitely talk to, uh, the...
well, I'll talk to everyone.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go to Ibiza.
What?
Ana said I've got a free room
at a hotel there, so...
You sure that's a good idea?
You've got like two weeks of
rehearsals left.
Yeah, it's a good idea.
-Are you sure... Yeah.
-Tim!
It's a good fucking idea, okay?
I need to go.
-I have to go there. You know?
-I understand that, Charli.
Because I need some
time to reset, you know?
And then it's
gonna be good for the tour
and for Brat  and for
literally everybody. Okay?
Because everybody's so desperate
for me to be fucking innovative
all the time
and fucking cool.
I don't have a fucking second
to my-fucking-self. You know?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-I made the album on my own.
I made it my fucking way,
and at that point in time,
no one fucking cared.
So everybody just left me alone
to do what I fucking
needed to do,
but now, every single person
is asking me questions
-all the fucking time.
-It's my job.
They're always like, "Charli,
do you wanna do something with
a green KitKat?"
And it's just like,
for fuck's sake. You know?
Everybody's always like, "What
do you want? What do you want?"
Well, I don't fucking know
what I fucking want, Tim.
[Tim] Yeah,
that all sounds fair.
Can we open a window?
Thanks.
Charli.
-Hey, babe. Hi.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-How you doing?
-Mmm. I'm good. -What
time'd you get back last night?
Midnight.
-It's, like, 7:00 a.m.
-It's okay. Yeah.
-You must be so exhausted.
-Can we talk about Johannes?
Or "Jo-hannes"? How the fuck
do you say this guy's name?
They're-- Alan-- Okay, he's
putting the bags in the car.
[Celeste] Why
are you up so early?
I am up because
I have to go to Ibiza.
-No, I know. I know.
-Right now?
Yeah. Yeah,
it's this whole thing.
-Ana booked it. -Charli,
we have a fucking rehearsal.
No, I know. I know, I know.
Ana booked it and
I can't get out of it
and it just became this
whole thing and I have to go.
It's like three, four days.
Tim said that you were gonna
be here all week for
the rehearsals.
I mean, Tim doesn't fucking
know anything, does he?
When has he ever known anything?
But-- I mean, please don't
be panicked about it.
It's gonna be fine. I mean,
you already said that we're
super far ahead anyways.
So I feel like you-- It's gonna
be great. It's gonna be fine.
Charli, after
yesterday, I'm really...
We're in a kind of
precarious situation.
-Uh...
-Like, this guy's vibe is weird.
I just don't
feel like he gets it
and now, like, the label's
involved, and I just don't--
Celeste, I feel like I've done
everything that I can do,
-and I really trust you...
-Okay.
...and so I need you to take
the lead on this right now,
you know?
Because everybody
wants this show to be massive
and, you know, if Amazon have
a problem with seeing my nipples
through my top,
or the fact that there's
a cocaine baggy on the poster,
then I'll just wear a different
top and we say it's
a sandwich bag
and it's not a big deal!
It's four days and I'll be back
before you know it.
It's... You're gonna do great.
Alan, let's go
quite quickly, yeah?
Okay.
Hi, Tammy.
Yeah, no, she is
on vacation apparently.
-Getting kind of peckish.
-Yeah.
Yeah, anything round here?
-Peri Peri Hut.
-Dead.
-Is that all there is?
-It's quite spicy.
There's Pret. There's...
I heard there's some...
I heard there's some bird living
in the building.
What?
-Yeah, in the bit above
the main stage. -Like a woman?
-The main stage? Wait, what?
-Who is she?
Well, that's what Melanie
on the front desk said.
-What, does she work here?
-Wait, wait, wait.
So they know about her and
they're just letting
her live here?
-What?
-That's illegal, innit?
Yeah.
Illegal?
No, no. I just--
I think they're trying to sort
it out, they just can't find it.
"It"? Fucking hell.
-That's all right, isn't it?
-It's a bit rude.
We're in the middle of bloody
nowhere. What does she even eat?
Rain and mice
and crumbs and stuff.
-She would eat mice?
-[Alex] You can't eat rain, Tim.
[wings flapping]
[Tim] Hello, Charli. It's me.
Sorry, it's me. I know we said
no work stuff while
you were away,
but I have just
been chatting to Celeste
and she had a couple of concerns
that did seem urgent enough to
warrant this.
Something about Johannes trying
to get you up in a harness
for some
wirework over the stage.
And she was like,
"Obviously Charli would never do
something like that."
So I thought it might just
be worth giving her a quick call
and ironing that out.
But mainly, enjoy yourself,
please, and I'll leave you alone
now. Sorry. Bye.
[chattering]
Welcome-- Gracias.
Welcome, Miss Aitchison.
-Hi.
-My name is Diana.
I will be your concierge
for your whole stay
and I'm sure you will have
a very relaxing time.
You have a tomorrow afternoon
appointment with Maria,
our holistic facialist.
-You're gonna love her.
She's amazing. -Yeah. Great.
Can I get you a snack,
something to drink?
No, I'm good.
I just wanna get to the room.
Sure.
[electronic
dance-pop music playing]
-Can you kill that?
-[music stops]
Um, is this, with my notes,
the draft from yesterday?
'Cause if it's too heavy,
you won't be able to see it on
the cam--
-Did you see Charli's
stories in Ibiza? -I have not.
It's like she's on the beach
and I'm just fucking stuck
here and--
-I know, but we have a lot
of work to do. -Yeah, you do.
I don't fucking
know why I'm here.
All right, let's just run it
from the strobing section.
[electronic
dance-pop music playing]
Hey.
Yes, I love this.
-Hey. How are you, Celeste?
-Hi. Hello.
-Hey. How's it going? How are
you doing? -I'm... I'm good.
How are you?
-I'm great. Thanks for asking.
-Great.
Do you have a minute? Just for--
I just have some-- couple of
ideas from a filmmaking
perspective.
-Um... -Super quick.
Just a couple of thoughts.
-Yeah, sure. Sure.
-[music stops]
-Can you guys give me five?
-Thank you, Celeste.
So, the-- I'm sensing
that these, um, super aggressive
lighting effects,
you're really into.
That it's, like, integral to
your idea,
your vision of the show that--
-Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
that's the show. -Yeah. Cool.
It's a little tricky to shoot,
you know? When you're
making a film.
Okay, um...
-So I-- I have a suggestion.
-Mm-hmm.
-[text alert buzzes]
-Are you familiar with...
with light-up wristbands?
-Like wristbands that light
up... -Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
-I am familiar, yeah.
-...and the audience wears them,
and then we can program
the wristbands to react to
the music, to the beat.
When you see it live...
-Right. Yeah. We're--
-...it'll blow your mind.
Coldplay have been
using them for years.
I'm sorry, we're just not
doing that.
That's-- That's-- We-- We--
It's supposed to
feel like a nightclub.
That is what we do.
That is what we are good at.
-Totally respect
that opinion obviously. -Okay.
Um, but I have to say
that I think we're just slightly
misaligned here.
[text alert buzzes]
-I'm trying to tell a story
here, okay? -Okay. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And a nightclub is not a story.
A nightclub is a nightclub.
Right.
And at some point,
the night has to end,
and they turn on the lights,
and you, like...
[makes crackling sound]
And then the next morning
you wake up, and it's like,
"Wow! My head is pounding.
What's happ-- Whoa," you know.
-Maybe you even
took illegal drugs. -Oh.
God forbid.
-Whereas a story...
-[text alert buzzes]
can be told and retold...
Yeah.
-...passed down from
fathers to sons. -Mm-hmm.
And obviously from
mothers to daughters as well.
-And so on and so forth.
-[text alert buzzes]
-That sounds amazing.
-It is. [chuckles]
-It's-- [sighs]
-[text alert buzzes]
It's just that the thing
about this show is actually--
the people that come to it,
for the most part,
-are just not--
-[buzzing continues]
are not that interested
in having children.
And some of them probably don't
even speak to their fathers
because they don't approve
of their lifestyle,
so it's like a whole different
thing that we're doing.
-You might not--
-[buzzing continues]
You might not get it,
which is totally fine.
Do you wanna take this?
If not, let's turn it off, okay?
[exhales]
All right, cool, guys.
Um, just carry
on. Lookin' great.
[Lloyd] You okay?
[Celeste] What the fuck?
[Johannes speaking, indistinct]
And it's like... I obviously
approached her with an open
spirit to collaborate.
Celeste was, like,
confrontational,
just shut me down...
Is this
a creative collaboration?
[continues speaking, indistinct]
[singer] ...doing
it, feeling it.
And I'm realizing that I'm
just starting to come alive.
-[phone buzzes] -Is there
anything I can get for you?
-Oh, can I get an Aperol Spritz,
please? - Hello?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
- Hey. Can you hear me?
-Hey, Celeste.
Sorry, that wasn't
for you, obviously.
Listen, I was just watching
a load of Johannes's stuff.
I think it's fucking awful.
Yeah, yeah. I'm really
happy to hear you say that.
I spent my whole night last
night trying to watch these
fucking tour films
and they're all the exact--
fuck-- same formula.
And what's crazy is that
they are just wildly popular.
He just has, like, a really,
like, sinister vibe. You know?
I didn't wanna tell you this,
'cause, like, it's just
something that I heard,
but I guess he's in, like, a
legal battle right now with Demi
and he's saying
he, like, owns her tour.
What? How the fuck
does that even work?
I don't know, but he's suing her
and apparently he's fucking
winning, which is even crazier.
Listen, Celeste,
I need you to make sure
that everybody knows
that we're doing
our tour creative, okay?
We can't do whatever the fuck
Johannes's version of this
would be.
I agree. I agree. Um...
I'm sorry to ask you to do this,
but do you think that you could
just send a quick email out
to everyone saying that
that's what we're doing
'cause, like, I'm having
a little trouble over here
getting
everyone on the same page.
Um, yeah. No problem.
-Of course I'll do that.
- Great. Thank you.
Don't wanna make you work
while you're trying to relax,
but it would be really,
really helpful for me.
[Charli] No, like, obviously.
I mean, thank you for
doing all of this stuff.
I'll speak to
you in a bit, yeah?
[Celeste] I'll
see you soon, bye.
[Morgh] Okay,
she'll call you later.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're stepping into a meeting.
Okay. Okay, bye.
Wait. Let me get--
Okay, Jamie, another lunch
which could have been an email,
I suppose.
What's the issue?
Tammy, well, firstly,
thanks for making the time.
It's just, we've been running
into a slight situation on
our end, and...
I wouldn't call it
a situation necessarily.
It's, uh, a tiny obstacle that
we can easily overcome together.
First, I wanna say
that I love the team.
They're amazing.
You know that I don't
subscribe to hierarchies.
We're all equals.
Um, but it might be good
to get a little bit of clarity
on the creative
hierarchy just here, I think.
Yeah, I think just because
Charli so often works with
Celeste,
they somehow got the idea
she would be collaborating on
this whole thing.
-Who?
-Uh, Celeste is Charli's...
-Friend, I guess?
-Yeah.
She has been quite hostile
to the creative energy
-that we were trying to
generate here.
-This isn't a collaboration.
Do you wanna collaborate?
You got a film to make, right?
-Yeah. -[Tammy] Johannes,
we will deal with this.
-Right?
-Yes. Yeah.
-Well, of course.
-Yeah.
Great.
[concierge] Oh, no, she is
very happy to appear on camera.
It's not
a problem for her at all.
Sessions with Maria
can be life-changing.
People wait for
years for an appointment.
Uh, really?
Isn't it just a facial, though?
[chuckles]
-Can I take your bag?
-Yeah, sure. Thanks.
-Right this way.
-Okay. Thank you.
-[remote beeps]
-[relaxing music plays]
[water trickling]
-[spa therapist] Good?
-Mm-hmm.
[spa therapist] Okay.
Thank you, Leonora.
Hello. Welcome to the space.
[Charli] Hi.
My name is Maria.
I'm an herbalist, a healer
and an holistic facialist.
[Charli] Wow, amazing.
Thank you so much for,
um, making time for me today.
I know it was a bit last-minute.
So, thank you.
[inhales deeply] Mmm. Mmm.
[Maria] Oh, I'm sorry.
-Oh, uh, are you-- Are you okay?
-[yawns]
Oh, oh, oh, oh. [clears throat]
When I'm yawning,
it's because I'm drawing out and
expelling all the stale energy
from your body. [chuckles]
And it's so very difficult
sometimes for the healer,
you know?
This is interfering.
Right, um... [clicks tongue] ...
I was just in the steam room for
three hours,
so I actually
feel pretty relaxed.
Well, sweetheart, you might feel
relaxed in your body,
but I can tell you, you are
completely closed in the heart.
I was wondering how you could
be walking around in that state.
I feel fine. I feel fine. Mmm.
Well, darling, your elasticity
is nearly zero.
-[Charli] Oh. -No,
I mean-- I mean, it's terrible.
-[speaking French] Oh là l.
-[inhales deeply]
[in English] I can tell you have
not been honoring your Saturn
return at all.
[clicks tongue] Um...
You know, as a woman,
it's a crucial time for you.
-Mmm. As a woman?
-[Maria] Yes.
-As a woman of your age...
-Right.
You should start the process of
preserving your body's beauty...
-Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-...you know?
Your skin is
telling you to slow down
before everything
just dries out.
I'm... [chuckles] ...not sure
I really agree with anything
you've just said.
-[Maria] Mmm. -I'm
doing a world tour, and what,
am I supposed to
just stop and disappear?
[scoffs] So you need the entire
world to know that you're
an artist
in order to make your art?
Um, no, I never said that.
Never. You-- You said that.
I didn't say that.
-I work with many
stars and musicians. -Mm-hmm.
Some of them you probably know.
-Mmm. Don't know about that...
-And they are not so defensive.
-I'm not sure I agree.
-Sorry.
I don't think I can treat you.
Great.
-Hello, Ms. Aitchison.
-Hi.
We are so sorry you couldn't
make it work with Maria
this time.
-This really never happens.
-[chuckles]
However, she was so kind
to prescribe these for you.
We have the Deflammation
Capsules,
the Balancing Peptide Crème,
Hyaluronic Acid,
Clarifying Retinol Mask and
the Daily Enzyme Enhancing Gel.
I will get these ready for you.
Great. Um...
How much is all of that?
[tense music playing]
Um...
Yeah, don't worry, I'll, uh--
I'll just get all of it. [sighs]
Sure.
-[sighs]
-[card reader beeps]
Um...
It-- It seems your card is not
working,
so maybe you want to try--
-You can just put
it on the room. -The room.
Yeah. Thank you.
[concierge] You are all set.
I really hope this helps you.
Thank you.
-[gasps] Oh, my God.
-Charli!
Hi.
-Hi. How are you?
-Hi, Kylie. Hi.
Um, I'm-I'm-- Yeah, I'm good.
What-What are
you doing here in Ibiza?
I'm about to do
my session with Maria.
Isn't she so good?
Uh-- Yeah. Yeah, she's amazing.
-I mean, I--
-[Kylie] So healing.
Mm-hmm. I feel so much better
than I did before, so...
Yeah. You look so good.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Oh, um... [chuckling]
I mean,
she said I was dry, so...
No. No, no. I mean like inside.
-Oh. Inside, yeah.
-You could tell.
No, but she's my favorite.
-Mmm.
-She's the best.
I literally come
here just to see her.
-I'm just so busy
these days, you know. -Yeah.
My kids, work and everything.
But I'm sure you know how it is.
You must be so busy.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, totally.
-Yeah.
But, yeah, I'm not a mother...
-Yeah. Um...
-...so it's a little different.
I've actually been
meaning to talk to you.
Um, I heard you're
working with Johannes.
I'm so jealous.
You know him?
Yeah. Um, yeah, my sister
introduced us, like, ages ago
and he was gonna do
some Hulu thing for us,
-but then he was busy...
-[Charli chuckles]
...with you!
-Oh.
-Yeah.
Ah, really? That--
-Yeah. I'm not mad at you.
-Oh, no. Good.
-I'm definitely not mad at you.
-That's good. Good.
No, I think it's amazing.
You're, like, leveling up.
-[Charli chuckles] -What's
that dance everyone is doing?
-Yes. The--
-The fruit?
-Apple. Yes. Yeah, yeah.
-Apples. Apples. So cute.
-[laughs]
-Thank you. Um...
It's funny you say that thing
about, um... [chuckles] ...
leveling up
because some people have been
telling me to kinda slow down,
maybe even disappear.
-No. No, bitch.
-No.
-Absolutely not.
-No, bitch. No.
No, it's not
funny. It's not funny.
Sorry.
That's crazy.
The second you think people
are getting sick of you,
-that's when you have
to go even harder. -Mmm.
If you're gonna do it,
you have to, like, do it.
-Do it.
-Right?
-Right. Right.
-Right.
You could totally be, like,
one of the best. Ever.
[Charli] Wow. Uh... [chuckles]
Yeah. Babe, this is exciting!
-No stress.
-Um...
-Yeah. No. No stress.
-So good.
-Just good, good vibes.
-We're here.
-Yeah. Yes.
-Yeah, good vibes.
I'm so happy for you.
-Oh. Thank you.
-Good to see you.
-Have a good session.
-I will.
-Oh, you just did.
-I did, yeah.
-Okay, love you. Bye.
Yeah, I love you--
Oh, my God.
Of course, you're fucking here.
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
[Charli] Hi, Tim. Hi, yeah. No,
no, no, everything's amazing.
Yeah, I'm having a great time.
No, no, no. I'm
feeling really relaxed. Yeah.
I don't know. It's a fucking
fountain. What do you think
it sounds like?
Listen! Listen, I'm just calling
because I wanna know
that everything is
all okay with Johannes.
What? I never said that
I didn't want him to do it.
Of course I want
him to fucking do it!
[line ringing]
Lloyd, can you hear me?
[Lloyd] Hello? Hold on. One
second, one second, one second.
Can you just go somewhere
where you can hear me, please?
-'Cause I need to fucking talk
to you. - Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on.
You need to make sure
that that man has every single
thing that he needs
to make this
fucking concert film, okay?
If he needs more money, we'll
give him more money. [stutters]
We'll get it from the Brat card.
We'll get it from the fucking
Brat card.
I can literally do a post
right this second.
Sorry, can you hear me, Charli?
Lloyd, we're doing a fucking
post for the Brat card, okay?
I have to tell everyone
to sign up for it or something.
What? Charli, like, for
the bank? Aren't you in Ibiza?
[Charli]  I can't be
half-assing this anymore,
and that means you have to do
your fucking job properly.
I need to level up! Fuck! Fuck.
[Lloyd speaks indistinctly]
Nothing. A glass broke.
-Did you send it?
- Yeah, one second. I gotta...
Isn't it just, like,
a photo and something about
the free tickets or...
Fuck! Tim, stay
on the fucking phone!
Wait. Just... Please,
stay on the fucking phone. Wait.
[Lloyd] But, like, why? You said
you weren't going to post
about it.
[Charli]
I changed my mind, okay?
The Brat show stuff
costs fucking money, Lloyd.
Tim, seriously, I'm putting my
body through so much
fucking stress
and it's causing me
permanent damage, okay?
Like my skin and my fucking
hair, Tim. I mean,
I've got zero elasticity.
Do you even know what
that means? Like,
it's really bad, apparently.
[phone buzzes]
-Okay, got it. Thank you.
-[Lloyd] Don't post
that one, okay?
That one was wrong.
Can you just hold on one...
Sorry, one second,
I just-- I'll be right there.
Charl--
[tense music building]
[sent tone chimes]
[sighs]
[message tone chimes]
[phone buzzes]
[intriguing music playing]
[vacuum cleaner buzzing]
[high-pitched buzzing]
[electricity powering down]
No, no. Exactly. I mean,
obviously he is the right person
to be doing this.
I can't believe I didn't
realize that at the beginning.
Yeah. Uh, thanks,
Tammy. You were right.
[sniffs]
Hi. Could someone
help me with my stuff?
[crew speaking indistinctly]
[technician
speaking indistinctly]
[Johannes] Nice.
Good work,
everyone. Ten minutes, lunch.
Can we see sort of
like a soft twinkle?
A little brighter.
Oh, nice. Nice. I like that.
Let's note this moment
for light-up wristbands.
-Hey.
-Hey, Celeste.
-How are you?
-I'm good. Um...
Charli's back today.
Can we go down, please?
-I'm sorry?
-[Celeste] Char--
[lift buzzing, beeping]
-Charli is back today.
-[Johannes] Charli's back?
-Yeah.
-Awesome.
I don't know what's going on
here, but I think we, uh, um...
You need to be prepared
to make some changes.
-[Johannes] Well,
I embrace changes. -Great.
Can only lose
what we cling to, right?
Yeah.
You saw Charli's email?
Uh, I don't do emails.
Okay.
Did you see it?
[Johannes] You know,
my father once said to me,
"Son, the only thing permanent
in this universe is
impermanence."
So let's embrace the change.
Sounds very wise.
Tim, can I just get an ETA
of when you guys are showing up,
because I just don't
want her to freak out?
All right, back off, everyone.
I'm in just kind of, like,
a situation with Johannes and
the label right now.
Hey, guys. Can
you get this out of here?
Johannes has taken over
the fucking space and it looks
like a goddamn lava lamp.
Um, but just give me a heads-up
because I'm trying to get it
cleared out before she arrives.
What is your ETA?
There's currently
a huge problem here.
Johannes has taken over
the whole fucking thing.
Oh, my God. Hi, hi, hi. Oh, my
God. Thank God that you're here.
-Hi.
-Thank God you're here.
He's a fucking disaster.
Johannes just moved
all of his stuff in here.
And I asked him to clear it up
before you arrived,
but nobody's fucking listening
to me anymore,
and I just, like--
-Have you been listening to me?
-[stutters] Uh--
I have, like, no
fucking authority here anymore.
Did you--
How was your trip?
-Um, it was great, thank you.
-Great.
It was really good, yeah.
-Did you send that email?
-Um...
'Cause he said he, like,
doesn't do emails. So...
Does-- Does that say "bitch"?
[Celeste] Um...
You know, I think it's
sort of, like, censored.
This is what he thinks
that your tour should look like.
I'm not exactly sure how
he's gotten all of this in here,
but I feel like he might
be, like, paying for it himself,
or, like, the label might be
paying for it,
which is even crazier.
-[Charli clears throat]
-Honestly,
it's been really confusing,
but now you're here,
and we can just get on with it.
-[Charli] "Get on with it"?
-Yeah.
[Charli] Tim, did you not
fucking figure out the...
[Celeste] Figure out what?
Yeah, um...
[chuckles]
Sorry, I'm a bit confused, so...
-What do you mean by "get
on with it"? -What do you mean?
Because, to me, that would mean
that we would have to start
again from scratch.
The show is in two weeks,
so I have to rehearse with his
stuff because this costs money,
do you know what I mean?
I can't just piss it all away
because now you're having second
thoughts, Celeste.
That's not how this works.
[Charli clears throat]
[chuckles] Um...
Are you paying for this?
You called me from Ibiza and
you said that you want to do
our show
and to make sure
that this didn't happen.
And listen, I understand
that this looks bad,
but it's not
starting from scratch.
-To be honest...
-Charli.
I think maybe you just
don't get it, Celeste.
[Tim gasps] Oh, my God.
-[walkie-talkie bleeps]
-Sorry.
Yeah. Don't worry,
that won't happen on--
Is that me?
[Celeste] That's
supposed to be you, yeah.
[Charli] I don't have
time for this, Celeste.
I have to do
stuff with him, okay?
-Can you just--
-Go for it. Yeah. Yeah.
Um-- Did-- [stutters]
Has Jamie had a chance
-to catch up with you, Celeste?
-[Johannes]
Hey! Hey! Welcome back.
How was Ibiza? My
home away from home.
-Did Jamie manage to
get ahold of you? -Yes.
Did you try any of
the beach clubs I recommended?
[Tim] You're
looking for answers...
I don't need to talk about
Jamie right now.
What the fuck does Jamie
have to do with any of this?
So let me walk you through
what we're doing here. Um...
[Charli] "Bitch." [chuckles]
No, that's a hashtag.
-Oh, okay.
-Um...
-Hi. You again.
-But yeah.
Do you wanna go check out
some renderings and stuff?
-I would love to.
-We got, um...
I'd love to do that.
-We got a new green.
-New green?
I love this one. So we've
gone with the uppercase B and--
You've changed the album cover?
It's slightly
more, like, earthy...
-Mmm, mm-hmm. Yeah.
-...you know.
'Cause the other one
was a bit "vomity," I guess.
Working on some outfits for you.
You're-- You're doing
the outfits? [chuckles]
-This is kind of-- I love this
one. -He does it all,
doesn't he?
[Charli] Right.
[Johannes] And I also think it's
a bit more age
appropriate for you.
I know you love cigarettes.
-We're keeping it edgy.
-[chuckles]
You can actually
step inside this lighter.
-[stammers] Really?
-As we set it on fire.
Is that safe then?
-A hundred percent
safe, of course. -Good. Okay.
All right. Here we go.
Back off, back off.
Safety distance, 25 feet.
[Charli, muffled] Why would I be
inside it if it was on fire?
[Johannes] And
three, two, one. Light it!
[Johannes chuckling]
-That was awesome. -[Charli]
How did it look? Did it go?
It was great. Okay.
Good job, everyone.
We have some dialogue
that I think could be quite
effective here.
You take a little moment
for audience interaction.
-Okay.
-So--
You wanna take
your glasses off maybe...
-Oh. Yeah. Yeah. -...so you can
really connect with people?
[sunglasses clatter]
So, you're like,
"Hey. Aw, thanks
for coming. Oh, my God."
Little interaction with
someone. "Hey, girls.
Where you guys from?
Oh, Japan. I love Japan.
Arigato for coming." You know?
[in high voice] Charli, Charli.
[imitates
screaming] We love you.
-Ah! [normal voice] And
they'd be pulling. -Yep, yep.
-[imitates screaming]
-Yeah, okay. Yeah.
-Hi.
-Oh, she's got a phone.
Uh...
-Grab it. Grab the phone.
-And take a picture.
-Yeah, of course. Sorry.
-The girls from Japan.
Yeah, and do something funny,
like, in the... in the selfie.
'Cause then it's like...
-it goes viral 'cause you're,
like... -Right.
I just don't think--
And what about
this... on your eye?
Yeah, I just-- Okay.
I mean, there's something
about that that just feels wrong
'cause they're from
Japan, but... Okay, yeah.
And then you go, "Tonight
means so much to me, Angels.
You know, making this album
has been amazing."
And then, just steady gaze
into the horizon.
[mimics shooting noise]
You are not to be messed with.
That kind of...
[clears throat]
"You know,
making this album
was such an amazing experience,
but it's not until now,
seeing it, feeling it..."
You know that, like,
"seeing it, feeling it."
That's got to, boom, land.
So it's like, [in British
accent] "But it's not until now,
seeing it, feeling it,
that I'm realizing it's only
just starting to come to life."
-[in normal voice] Just try it.
-Mm-hmm.
Brat is so much
bigger than an album.
[chuckles]
-It's bigger than me. -[Johannes
chuckling] Yeah, yeah.
[Charli] Mm-hmm.
"It's bigger than all of us."
[flatly] Brat Summer forever.
No. No?
It's okay. I just...
I'm not sure I feel that it's
gonna last forever.
-I'm like-- Give me forever.
-Okay. Okay, let me... Yeah.
[shouts] Brat Summer forever!
You sound a little hysterical
there. Just a little bit.
So maybe just,
like, more powerful,
-less, like,
[shrilly] "forever." -Yep.
"Brat Summer forever!"
And you can hold this pose
for a good five to ten seconds
'cause the audience
will go nuts.
Great. Oh, well, okay. I...
So, do you want me to run it?
[Johannes] Yeah,
from the top. Have fun with it.
[Charli] Um...
-After you. Just a quick chat.
-Sorry.
[Jamie] Okay.
-It's kinda cold.
-Yeah.
I like the way you've hung
your lanyard there. It's cool.
-Yeah. What's up?
-[sighs]
Here it is. Basically, it's--
We're all extremely grateful for
the hard work you've put into
the show so far.
[Celeste] Okay.
And it's just... [sighs]
We really have to prioritize
a successful concert film at
the end of the day.
Totally.
We just-- We really need
Johannes to take the lead
on this.
That psychopath?
[stammers] Is anybody
looking out for her? Tim?
When Charli was in Ibiza,
she called me and she said,
"Do not let this happen."
And now I don't know
what the fuck is going on.
Yeah, the thing is, Celeste,
you don't need to know what
the fuck is going on.
Because this is Charli's show
and this is all coming directly
from Charli.
She's completely on board
with Johannes. Okay?
Look, she even...
she even called Tammy herself
to say how
excited she was about it.
So what
the fuck am I doing here?
Honestly, I don't even know.
It's probably best
to just call it a day, Celeste.
-[Tim] Yeah, thank
you so much, really. -Mmm.
-[Tim clears throat]
-Can we just crack on? Please.
[Josh] You absolutely
bossed that.
[Jamie sniffs] Thanks, man.
[door closes]
[pensive music playing]
[fluttering]
[thuds]
[crew chattering]
[Lloyd] Is that a cigarette?
Towards you. Towards you.
Push it. Push it.
-Yeah, sorry, sorry, sorry.
-We should be dragging it,
shouldn't we?
[crew chattering]
Morning.
Beautiful day.
Every day is gorgeous, every
day is a blessing, of course,
but today feels special.
Is she going to, like,
ride it or something?
[Charli grunts]
[Ted] What, is that feeling
tight? It looks tight.
Um, it's... [grunts]
...digging in a little bit.
Well, that could
cut off your circulation.
-Oh.
-You could lose a toe.
-So, we're too tight?
-[strap whips]
[Ted] Let's,
uh, try another bag.
Stick another 10
kg on, please, boys.
Uh, how high up are we going?
Oh, high as you like, love.
I've done right up to
the rafters quite a few times.
Audience go mad for that.
It's an incredible view.
Right. Talent ready to fly.
Moving. Let's get her up.
[Johannes] Yeah, here we go.
[Ted] Keep it steady, please.
[Charli breathes deeply] Tim.
[Tim] Whoa.
I want a go. [chuckles]
I need you to be honest
and tell me if this looks shit.
No. I think it's sort
of, like, ethereal. Yeah.
-[Charli] Really?
-[Ted] You all right up there?
Uh, yeah. I'm good, thank you.
Tim, will you please tell me if
this looks fucking shit? Does
it look shit?
No, I...
Charli, I just think if it feels
like you, then it's gonna be
great, you know.
I don't know what that fucking
means, Tim. [breathes deeply]
-Yeah. Yeah. -Looks
great. Looks great. Love it.
Okay, cue the track.
I look like a fucking idiot.
[breathes deeply]
["I might say something stupid"
playing through speakers]
♪ I might say something stupid ♪
♪ Talk to myself in the mirror ♪
♪ Wear these
clothes as disguise ♪
♪ Just to reenter the party ♪
♪ Door is open
Let in, but still outside ♪
♪ I look perfect
for the background ♪
♪ I get nervous, sip the wine ♪
♪ I go so cold, I go so cold ♪
♪ And I don't know ♪
♪ If I belong
here anymore, I... ♪
[phone buzzing]
[Tim] Jamie, no. Sorry.
Two secs. I can't right now.
Bye. Two minutes.
[Lloyd] What
the fuck is she doing?
[Charli sighs]
[breathing deeply]
[crew member] I've got someone
called Tammy here at
the security gate.
There's a big group of them.
They're saying they have access.
Sorry, what?
Charli's in rehearsal right now.
What... What do
you mean outside? Outside where?
No, it's good, it's good.
It's good, it's good.
[breathes deeply]
[music swells]
[Charli singing through
speakers] ♪ I don't know if
I belong here anymore ♪
♪ I don't know if
♪ If I belong here anymore ♪
♪ I don't know if ♪
♪ I belong here anymore ♪
[Johannes] Goose bumps.
Uh, let's go again, and without
the long, boring intro,
okay? Right away.
-[Charli] Uh, okay. Great.
-There's some people from
the label...
[Johannes] We need to
get her above the lighter.
[Ted] Sure thing. We just need
to reset a couple of things.
Is it all right if we just
let her hang tight for a minute?
Higher.
-[Tammy] Tim!
-[rigging buzzing]
-Tim!
-[Ted] All right, Charli.
I'll need you to stay put,
and I'm gonna sort this out.
-[crew member] Hey, wait.
-Fuck.
-Tim. We need to talk. Now!
-Hello!
[Tim] Okay, hi.
-Were you aware of this post?
-[Charli] What did I... What?
-What post? Social? What
social... -The social post
wherein which Charli
inaccurately advertised
the Brat card partnership...
Tim, what's happening?
-...and subsequently...
-Sorry.
...voided the whole deal!
-Did you sign off on that?
-No.
-Lloyd! Lloyd.
-Oh, my God!
Charli's crashed
the fucking bank! Fuck!
What?
-Sorry. Is this the gay card?
-[Ted] Talent in descent!
-Is this the gay credit card
thing? -Can you put me down?
-Can I just have clarity?
-Get your artist down!
Okay, I plan to get her down,
but can I just get clarity?
[Tammy] Come here, little girl.
We need to talk.
Can we find a quiet space?
-[Tim] I reckon
we potentially ... -Do you know
where a quiet space is?
...utilize the...
the dressing rooms.
What the fuck? Why is
she dressed like Tinker Bell?
-[Jamie] There's not a door.
-[Tim] The door is over there.
[Jamie] That's just
where two people are standing.
Can someone please
explain to the director
-what's going on? -[Tammy]
You are not allowed to share...
God, Morgh!
-What is this? What is this?
What is this? -[grumbles] God.
[Pauline] Okay, okay. This
is a very sensitive situation.
Can anybody not involved in
the Howard Stirling partnership
please get out?
[Lloyd] Listen,
everybody. Relax.
Who are you?
The bank is not crashing. Okay?
They're saying that there's
a small possibility that--
-[Tammy] Who told you that?
-[Molly] Is Charli getting
canceled?
That the bank might,
might crash. This bank was
fucked already, right?
-[Tim] Oh, shit.
-[Lloyd] Right?
It's all over the Internet.
Yes, Tim. It's all
over the fucking Internet.
Charli misrepresented
this whole thing.
That's the fuckup that we're
dealing with, okay? Rashid,
just... Listen.
So, the artist
shared a social post
which incorrectly advertised
the terms and conditions
as per the contract
with the bank.
[Charli] But Lloyd, I just
posted what you told me to post.
Many of the artist's fans signed
up just to get the free ticket,
and now these individuals are
defaulting on their initial
payments.
[Tammy] Your fans aren't paying
their credit card bills, Charli!
What about the fraud? The fraud.
Yeah. So they used multiple
forms of identification,
which is basic fraud.
-There have been some arrests.
-[Lloyd] Arrests?
[Charli] This isn't my fault.
This is obviously
the bank's fault.
We're not speculating about
personal liability right now.
I signed up for two cards.
Am I going to prison?
-But it's obviously
not my fault! -Charli, stop--
Charli! We were not even in
the same country when
you posted that.
Lloyd! Get away
from me! Get away from me!
-Get away from me! Get away from
me! -[Lloyd] Why aren't
you helping me?
-This is not on me. -Yes
it is! This is not my fault!
Calm down! I'm
becoming concerned now! Okay.
Less of that.
Okay. We're going to get Charli
out to her car.
We're going to get her out of
here. Ana, can you call
the driver and grab--
-Sorry, sorry. Just-- Just--
-[Tammy] Tim. Tim, Tim, Tim.
No, no, no, no. Tim!
I don't think that's a good
idea. I don't think it's wise.
That's not wise.
-Where are you going?
-Where is he going?
Well, that's brat
summer fucking over.
[Tammy mumbles]
-[glass smashes]
-[Tammy] Whoa.
-Great.
-Okay. I'm just gonna...
-[Charli breathes heavily]
-You good?
-Can you just close the...
please. -Okay, sorry.
Sorry. Um...
Thank you.
Fuck!
What the fuck? What the fuck?
[breathing heavily]
[distorted]
♪ Party girl, party girl ♪
Fuck!
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[objects clattering]
Fucking dates. Fucking joke...
Pitchfork.
[sighs, groans]
[breathing heavily]
[melancholy music playing]
[sighs]
[reporter 1]  Financial
institution Howard Stirling
have finally filed for
bankruptcy after an unstable
few years.
This collapse follows
a polarizing rebranding for
the bank
in their attempts to target
a younger demographic.
Fans have been expressing their
frustration and disappointment
in the wake of the "Brat card
crash," as it has been
dubbed online.
[reporter 2] This is a real fall
from grace for this artist.
Charli xcx has lost
almost one million followers
in the wake of this
Brat card controversy.
[Colbert] Bad news
for, uh, Brat fans.
Sounds like Charli xcx might be
in trouble with Charli SEC.
[commentator]  Ugh,
I mean, it's so transparent.
Charli isn't counterculture.
She just steals from it to try
to look cool without actually
saying anything.
...decided to revise my Brat
score from a ten to a three.
Everyone's asking
about Charli. Uh...
Honestly, I... I just
feel really bad for her fans.
"I'm So Julia." [scoffs] Yeah,
right. That is not what
I'm about.
[Colbert] Now, there was one
hint that the bank might be in
trouble early on
when the Brat card sign-up bonus
was a free bag of cocaine.
[studio audience laughing]
I don't think someone named
Charli xcx and her gay-ass
credit card...
Get her.
[reporter 1] Howard Stirling was
in an extremely insecure place,
and their attempts to capitalize
on a young, vulnerable market
clearly backfired.
You, like, analyze. Oh, my God.
How could I be friends with
a person who could do something
like this? Uh...
[fan] I used to be one of
Charli's biggest fans,
but after all of
this, I just can't.
Everything I had,
all my savings are gone.
Honestly, I don't really know
what to say.
She used to mean so much to me.
[vlogger] The better question
instead of "Who killed
Brat Summer?"
is "Who owns Brat Summer?"
What is it? How did it happen?
And was it ever something
purely devoid of commerciality
which supposedly killed it
in the first place?
I'll be exploring this in
today's video while charting
the album rollout
to analyze how pop's
most intuitive Internet starlet
has won this
year's viral Olympics.
[high-pitched buzzing]
[Tammy] Okay, we're all here, so
let's not waste any more time.
Where are we at?
[Rashid] Well, uh, with
regards to the Howard Stirling
situation,
our main concern is still
the concert ticket promotion.
[inhales sharply] Uh...
As the tickets have already been
distributed, they remain valid,
but the bank have made it clear
that they are not gonna pay
for them.
[Tammy] Ah, because the bank
no longer exists.
That is correct.
So if the tour goes ahead,
we're paying for these little
gay criminals to watch it?
-[Tammy] Huh?
-[Rashid] The... I wouldn't...
[Tammy] Okay,
okay. I got it. I got it.
We're gonna have to
find a way to recoup.
What's the situation
with Amazon?
Oh, they are locked-in.
That deal is solid.
-[Tammy] That's good.
-Yeah.
Tammy, if I may interject as
well, just a reminder
that that was us.
-The Amazon...
-[Tammy] Oh.
-Thank you.
-[Tim] What was you?
-What? -Uh, I'm
sorry. Johannes is here.
-What? Johannes? For what?
-Johannes?
This fucking guy.
-I told her that you're in
a meeting. -All right. Just...
All right, just bring him in.
Bring him in.
-What the fuck?
-Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hey.
Oh, great.
Everyone's here. [chuckles]
You guys are
in a bit of a tough situation.
So maybe this is a good time for
us to discuss my involvement
with the film.
Well... [chuckles]
...what's there to discuss?
Well, uh, Tammy, the context of
the project has clearly changed.
Bruce, you can jump in if
you feel like you wanna add
something here.
When my client, Johannes
was attached to this film,
he did not agree to making
seditious promotional materials
for a figure of
political unrest.
[Johannes] Exactly.
It has become clear that this
film would be in aid of
an agenda
that is at odds with
the moral standing of my client.
-[Johannes] Yes.
-[chuckles] Moral standing?
-[Bruce] Mm-hmm.
-[Tammy laughs]
[stammers] I don't care if--
if Charli fucked the Unabomber,
you're under a fucking contract.
I cannot be
associated with a communist!
She's hardly a communist.
She did a bloody H&M campaign.
I'm sorry, but this... this
whole situation is perverse.
She is perverted.
She has bankrupted her own fans.
You think they're
gonna go watch her show?
Johannes, mate, there is still
quite a lot of interest,
actually.
-[Josh] Apparently,
a lot of her fans... -In what?
...think the whole
thing's quite funny.
[Johannes] What?
-[Tammy] Yes. And, Tim...
-Ha ha.
Yeah. Well, Charli is going
on the road, doing the shows.
Right, Tim? Right?
Um, I'm actually giving
her a bit of space at the
moment, um, since everything.
So you haven't spoken to Charli?
Since when?
I said since everything happened
with this.
Well, that was... [stammers]
-Since last week? -[Rashid]
Probably like a week, yeah.
[Tim] What's this week?
-Yes. Yeah, yeah. Yeah. -Wait,
so has anyone talked to Charli?
Huh? No?
If Charli isn't
here, there's no show.
Where does that leave us?
Well, if the artist is
responsible for canceling
their own show,
um, due to
illness or incapacity,
or perhaps sudden death,
they are, or their estate is,
responsible for the costs of
that cancellation.
What... So, what, sudden death?
Okay. So she's not
dead, we can assume.
[church bell tolling]
Yeah.
[tense music playing]
Oh.
Um...
Wait. Can we do
with five minutes?
Sorry, I'm being weird.
Um...
[tense music building]
-[exclaims] Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
-[groans]
-[exhales sharply]
-[elevator voice] Doors closing.
-[Lloyd] There you are. Hi.
Whoa. -[exclaims] Fucking hell!
You've heard from Charli,
right? You've like...
You've seen Charli?
No. Not since Thursday.
Ana! What the fuck?
-[Lloyd] Tim, tone. Dude,
what... -Yeah, yes, sorry. I...
That's really
rude. I'm sorry. Just...
They think she's dead.
-They think she might be dead.
-Who thinks she's dead?
The label thinks she's...
-People think she's dead?
-Yes. No, no. Please, I--
If I may... Uh...
Uh, if she's missing...
[stammers] ...uh,
there's no show. Correct?
-[Tim] She could just be out.
-We should post, like,
a missing thing,
-right? -[Ana]
You know of her house in London?
She has a house in London?
No, she doesn't. What?
-[Lloyd] It should be
a black screen? -Where?
-Not like a picture of her.
-No! Not posting about this!
Are you mad?
-I booked an Uber.
-Yeah. Do book an Uber.
-You have. Yeah, brilliant.
-Yeah, it's--
One thing.
Hypothetically,
if something has...
[knocks on table]
...God forbid,
happened to Charli,
are we in control of the footage
that's already been shot? Or...
We are. Okay.
[church bell tolling]
-[Lloyd] It's this one?
-[Ana] Yes.
[Tim] Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
-Thank you.
-[Ana] Come on.
-[Tim] Thank you. Thank you.
-[Lloyd grunts]
-Ow. [grunts]
-[Tim] Is it that house?
[Johannes chuckles]
Did you guys
ever see the Amy movie?
You gotta wa...
It's incredibly powerful.
[church bell continues tolling]
[crows cawing]
[Tim speaking indistinctly]
[footsteps running]
[all breathing heavily]
-[Ana] Oh, fuck.
-[Lloyd] Oh, Jesus Christ.
[disjointed,
indistinct dialogue]
[static buzzing]
[tense music building]
-[Ana] Charli?
-[Charli gasps]
[Tim gasps]
[sighs]
[church bell tolling]
[Charli sighs]
[Tim] Um, no, just sleeping.
She said she was tired. Yeah.
No. No, no, she completely
understands. Yeah.
Johannes's show.
Whatever he wants to do.
No, no. No notes,
as far as I'm aware.
Uh...
Yeah, no, she's sure.
[birds chirping]
[pensive music playing]
[Tim] Okay. Cheers.
[Celeste] Um... [smacks lips]
No. I haven't. Um...
But she sent me this voice note.
Let me see if
I can get this hooked up here.
[sighs]
[sniffs]
[phone beeps]
Hey, Celeste. Um... [inhales
sharply] ...It's me. [chuckles]
I, uh...
[breathes shakily]
I'm sorry about... um...
about everything.
Uh...
[sighs] I'm sure
you saw what happened.
I mean, it was all pretty
terrible, actually. [chuckles]
I know this whole thing's become
a bit of a joke now,
and I've become a bit of a joke.
[inhales sharply]
And I don't think
I would forgive me,
so I don't expect you
to forgive me, obviously.
Um...
But I just wanted to say that
I'm really, really sorry.
It's funny. [sighs]
This whole summer,
I've been dreading the end.
I don't know, I just...
I built this tour up
to be something so massive.
I got so caught up
in all of it. [sighs]
I've spent my whole
life trying to get...
approval or something.
Trying to get in... [scoffs]
...trying to be cool.
[groans] It's just...
God, it's just so fucking
embarrassing trying so hard all
the time. [chuckles]
[sighs]
So when I felt like people
started to care about me...
[chuckles]
...nothing else
mattered, you know?
Nothing was more important than
getting people to keep on buying
into Brat.
Getting more and more people to
like it. It didn't even matter
if I liked it.
I didn't even think about that.
I just didn't want it to stop.
I know it's not chic to be
the last person at the party,
but, um...
I think I hate going home.
Yeah, I... I really hate it.
[sniffles]
I guess I just thought that
if enough people liked me
or at least
paid attention to me,
that maybe I would look
in the mirror and like myself.
[sniffles]
But I didn't.
Sorry, um... [chuckles]
You probably already know
I'm doing the show. [chuckles]
Not our show,
Johannes' show. Um...
It's just something that I need
to do, and I hope you get why.
You're probably the only person
who would get why.
But I need you to know this
isn't me giving in or anything.
I'm doing it, uh,
this hideous fucking show,
not to keep Brat going,
but to destroy it,
-to let it die.
-Camera two. Wide.
[Charli] We always knew
we'd have to kill it anyways.
Maybe there's a world where
we could have done it our way,
but that is
just too far gone now.
And I know that that's my fault.
[breathes shakily]
Anyways,
you should come. [chuckles]
Um...
I mean, it really does look like
a fucking lava lamp.
I'm not offending
anyone. Nightmare.
Obviously, it's all
fucking ridiculous and sad...
...but I don't have to worry
about it being cool anymore,
or if it feels like me
because it has nothing to do
with me anymore.
In a way, I feel kinda good.
Like free.
Or something.
[sighs]
It's like I'm not being dragged
along by this thing anymore.
I finally got
a piece of myself back.
["Bittersweet Symphony" playing]
Everyone else can make
Brat Summer last forever if
they want to,
but for me, it's over.
[chuckles]
And, um...
you can't dread
the end when it's over.
Sorry this was so long. Uh...
Gonna send this now. Um...
Okay. Bye.
["Bittersweet Symphony"
continues]
[Johannes] What does that say?
"Communist cum dump?"
Jesus Christ.
Okay, reframe camera three.
I can't use that, okay?
Camera three, are you fucking
deaf? Can you reframe?
♪ 'Cause it's
a bittersweet symphony ♪
♪ That's life ♪
♪ Trying to make ends meet ♪
♪ You're a slave to
money then you die ♪
♪ I'll take you down ♪
♪ The only road
I've ever been down ♪
♪ You know the one
that takes you To the places ♪
♪ Where all
the veins meet, yeah ♪
♪ No change, I can change
I can change, I can change ♪
♪ But I'm here in my mold
I am here in my mold ♪
♪ But I'm a million different
people From one day to
the next ♪
♪ I can't change my mold
No, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ Have you ever been down? ♪
♪ Been down? ♪
♪ Ever been down? ♪
♪ Have you ever been down? ♪
[song fades]
[crowd cheering]
["Dread" playing]
[song ends]